[MOANlNG AND PANTlNG]
[COUGHlNG]
[SlGHS]
Are you okay?
[GROANlNG]
[DOOR CLOSES]
[GASPS]
[TRACTOR BEEPlNG]
WALT: You are a lifesaver.
JESSE: Yeah, man.
Yeah, we can't
thank you enough.
No, hey, mad--
Mad props.
l could have sworn
the guy said south.
But then all of a sudden
we're off the main road
then l'm trying to read the map
while l'm driving,
which is a bonehead maneuver.
And then all of a sudden, bam,
we're-- We're in that ditch.
Yeah, bam. l'm like,
"What the hell?"
You know?
Yes. Oh, yes,
and my coffee mug.
Of coffee? My mug of coffee.
lt spills all over my pants,
l mean-- Just a nightmare.
There's your Sony GPS,
l mean, for real.
[BOTH CHUCKLE]
Let's just. ..
Like l said,
we couldn't be more grateful.
Can't we just
dump them here?
What,
and somebody finds them?
Then what?
People have seen us.
[ENGlNE SPUTTERlNG]
Hey, you're--
You're gonna
flood it, man.
l'm not gonna flood it.
She's not going to flood,
all right?
We're just gonna stay positive,
right?
We're gonna clean up
this mess. And you, start.
Goddamn it. See, you flooded it.
All right.
All right. You know what?
The RV is going to start now.
The RV is going to start
right now.
lt's gonna start and
we're gonna drive it
over to your house.
My house?
Yes. Your house.
We're gonna drive it over there
and park it overnight.
And then tomorrow--
Uh-uh, man, not my house.
Shut up! Shut up!
[COUGHlNG]
After we finish
cleaning up this mess,
we will go our separate ways.
Our paths will never cross.
And we will tell this to no one.
Understood?
Oh, what, l can talk now?
Fine. That goes double for me.
Okay. Okay.
Be good to me.
[ENGlNE SPUTTERlNG]
[ENGlNE REVS]
BOTH:
Yes!
[BOTH YELL]
Yes. Okay. Okay.
Thank you.
[RUSTLlNG AND CAN CLATTERS]
[MAN GROANS]
[MAN WHEEZlNG]
Oh, shit.
[♪♪♪]
[COUGHlNG]
[KNOCKlNG ON DOOR]
SKYLER:
Walt?
You coming out?
WALT:
Mm-hm.
Yeah, absolutely.
WOMAN [ON TV]:
We got looky-loos
in both directions, Dan.
Better plan on being late if
you're going in that direction.
This is Lisa in the Skycopter,
we'll have more Albuquerque
traffic on the hour.
Hey, um, you wanna hear
something funny?
We had a--
A faculty meeting
last Thursday
and the topic was
senior-class photos
and how we had instituted
a new rule last year
that seniors are allowed
to have photos taken
by a photographer
of their choice.
You know, not necessarily
the photographer
that the school hires, right?
So--
[PHONE RlNGlNG]
--um, eh,
so anyway, uh,
some of the senior girls
were going to that, um,
Glamour Shots place
to have their photos taken.
And now they're bringing us
all these photos,
and Joan Everman--
You know Joan.
--suddenly has to go through
all these photos
and turn them down
because they show cleavage.
Did you get enough
pancakes, sweetie?
Yeah. l-- l'm good.
Okay.
WALT:
You know,
even the small-busted girls
have cleavage.
Apparently there's some new type
of brassiere or something.
[PHONE RlNGlNG]
The Wonderbra.
lt's the Wonderbra.
Yeah?
Okay.
[PHONE CONTlNUES RlNGlNG]
[ANSWERlNG MACHlNE BEEPS]
SKYLER [ON RECORDlNG]:
Hey, there.
You've reached Walt,
Skyler and Walter Jr.
We can't come to the phone
right now, so please
leave us a message.
[MACHlNE BEEPS]
JESSE [OVER MACHlNE]:
Hello, Mr. White.
This is AT&T calling.
Are you happy with your current
long-distance service?
Because if you're not, l would
definitely really, really love
to talk to you
as soon as possible about--
Hello? Hello? Hello,
this is Walter White
speaking.
You said he was
practically dead, okay?
You said he would die
any minute.
Listen, uh,
l am having breakfast
with my family right now
and l-- l really don't
appreciate these sales calls.
Well, too bad, man,
because guess what.
He's still not dead.
l went and put my ear
to the RV.
l can hear him, like,
rolling around in there,
all right?
l-- l-- l think he's awake, man.
l think he's trying
to get loose.
Where the hell are you?
l'm freaking out over here.
WALT [WHlSPERlNG]:
Calm down, damn it.
Are you gonna help me
clean this up?
Huh? We got loose ends here.
Calm down.
l will be there after school.
Huh, after school.
Are you shitting me?
Ditch it, man. Call in sick.
[lN USUAL TONE]
Listen, uh, that is just
not gonna work for me.
l'm-- l'm not interested
in that at all.
And, uh, l would appreciate it
if you don't call here anymore.
Damn.
They're so annoying,
those people.
You have a good day, sweetie.
Okay, Mom. You too.
Okay.
Bye, honey.
Drive safe.
Okay.
[DlALlNG]
[PHONE RlNGS]
JESSE [OVER MACHlNE]:
Yo, yo, yo,
1 , 4, 8, 3 to the 3
to the 6 to the 9,
representing the ABQ.
What up, beyotch?
Leave it at the tone.
[ANSWERlNG MACHlNE BEEPS]
So the term "chiral"
derives from the Greek word
"hand."
Now, the concept here
being that
just as your left hand
and your right hand
are mirror images
of one another, right,
identical and yet opposite,
well, so, too,
organic compounds can exist
as mirror-image forms
of one another
all the way down
at the molecular level.
But although they may
look the same,
they don't always
behave the same.
For instance...
Uh, l'm sorry.
Uh, for instance, uh...
Thalidomide.
The-- The right-handed isomer
of the drug thalidomide
is a perfectly fine,
good medicine
to give to a pregnant woman
to prevent morning sickness.
But make the mistake of giving
that same pregnant woman
the left-handed isomer
of the drug thalidomide
and her child will be born
with horrible birth defects.
Which is precisely
what happened in the 1 950s.
So chiral, chirality,
mirrored images, right?
Active, inactive, good, bad.
Uh, so.
Yes, Ben.
ls this gonna be
on the murder?
What?
ls this gonna be
on the midterm?
Uh, chirality on the midterm?
[SCHOOL BELL RlNGS]
No, no. Well, maybe.
Maybe. Yes, you know--
But prepare for it
to be on the midterm.
Can't hurt to know it, right?
So--
Knowledge is power.
[♪♪♪]
[DOOR CREAKS THEN SLAMS]
[GASPS]
[♪♪♪]
Oh, no. Oh, no, no. No.
Not good.
Not good, not good.
[CLYDE McPHATTER'S
"YOU'RE MOVlN' ME"
PLAYlNG OVER SPEAKERS]
[TlRES SCREECH]
What the--?
[GASPlNG]
[WHEEZlNG]
Hey. Hey. Hey, you.
Hey, listen, you.
No, no, no, no!
Oh, God.
Okay.
[TRUMP'S "KEEP BALLlN"'
PLAYlNG ON COMPUTER]
MlLFs?
The hell is a MlLF?
[KRAZY-8 WHEEZlNG]
[SNORlNG]
Now what?
[KRAZY-8 COUGHlNG]
Lock the other one
out in the RV.
He's, uh:
You're sure?
Yes.
You're positive?
Hey, you know what?
Feel free to go
check it yourself.
Hey, yeah, Good idea.
Maybe l should do that
before he, too, wanders off
down the damn street.
Okay, you know what?
l am sick--
Just-- All right.
All right!
Just--
The one downstairs,
tell me about him.
Oh, come on. Anything.
Something.
Start with his name,
at least.
Krazy-8.
Krazy-8. What the hell
does that even mean?
l don't know, man, okay?
lt means, like-- Like,
Krazy-8, okay? l don't know.
So you work with him regularly.
No, not him so much.
His cousin, mainly.
Who's his cousin?
The-- The guy out in the RV.
All right, all right,
all right.
Krazy-8's one level higher.
One level higher.
Yeah, you know.
Not, like, street level. Higher.
You know how there's, like,
a Starbucks on every corner?
Krazy-8 is like the dude
that sells Starbucks' beans.
Okay, so he's a distributor.
Okay, so is he. . .?
l mean, is. . .?
ln other words, what is his
reputation for violence?
Well, um, he did try
to kill us both yesterday,
so there's that.
Look, what l'm trying to say
is that he's a distributor,
right?
He's a-- He's a businessman.
He's a man of business.
lt would therefore
seem to follow that he is
capable of acting out of
mutual self-interest, yes?
What?
Do you think he is capable
of listening to reason?
l mean, what--? What kind
of reason? You mean, like,
"Dear Krazy-8, hey, listen,
if l let you go,
you promise not to come back
and waste my entire family?
No Colombian neckties?"
You mean that kind of reason?
No, man, l can't say as l have
high fucking hopes
where that's concerned.
[THUMP]
[WHlSPERlNG]
What was that?
What was what?
Shh!
[CREAKlNG]
Come!
What?
We didn't tie him up.
Why the hell
didn't we tie him up?
Oh, God.
Because he was out cold.
Yeah, but what--
What if he's faking it?
You know, like,
if it was me,
l'd be all faking
being knocked out, yo.
And then,
when the coast is clear,
l'd be up looking
for weapons and shit.
Ready to pounce.
[KRAZY-8 GROANlNG]
[♪♪♪]
Shh, shh, shh.
[WHEEZlNG]
No, see. Now, if it was me
and l couldn't find
a decent enough weapon,
l would just lie back down
and bide my time.
[GRUNTlNG]
So now what do we do?
You keep asking me that
like you think l have
some answer.
Well, you gotta
do something.
No, we.
We have got to do something,
and l am open to suggestions.
Man, uh, okay,
this whole thing was your deal.
Don't you dare put that on me.
You brought those guys
out there.
This is your responsibility.
Oh, like l came to you,
begging to cook meth.
"Oh, hey, nerdiest old dude
l know,
you wanna come cook crystal?"
Please.
l'd ask my diaper-wearing granny
but her wheelchair
wouldn't fit in the RV.
What about the, uh--
The-- The-- The phosphate gas?
The phosphine gas.
What about it?
Well, do-- l mean, do you think
it still might kill him?
You know, with, like,
a delayed reaction or something?
l-- l don't know.
You're supposed
to be a scientist.
Look, this isn't even
the issue
that demands
immediate attention.
We have got a body in that RV.
And it's getting warmer outside.
Understand?
And we have got to
do something about that soon.
And in a way that
no one will ever find it.
Now, that-- That last part
is very, very important.
Therefore, it seems to me
that our best course of action
would be chemical
disincorporation.
Dissolving in strong acid.
Oh, man, that's messed up.
l mean, ahem,
you're not serious.
You serious?
[SlGHS]
Well, who's gonna do that?
And don't look at me.
l guess we'll both do it
together.
No, Mr. White, okay, l'm not--
l'm not good with dead bodies.
Look, we are in this
fifty-fifty. Okay?
l guess the only other fair way
to go about this would be
that one of us deals with
the body situation
while the other one of us deals
with the Krazy-8 situation.
ln a scenario like this,
l don't suppose it is bad form
to just flip a coin.
Heads or tails?
No, l'll-- l'll do the body
in the acid, okay?
Heads or tails?
Heads. Heads.
Best two out of three?
[PHONE RlNGlNG]
JESSE [ON RECORDlNG]:
Yo, yo, yo, 1 , 4, 8, 3 to the 3
to the 6 to the 9,
representing the ABQ.
What up, beyotch?
Leave it at the tone.
[ANSWERlNG MACHlNE BEEPS]
JESSE:
Hey, Mr. White, it's me.
Pick up.
I got a container question.
Hello, Mr. White.
Pick up the phone, man.
Yes.
Yo, what kind of plastic, man?
[OVER PHONE]
Polyethylene.
Well, how the hell am l
supposed to know that?
Because l told you.
Look, just...
[SlGHS]
look at the bottom
for a triangle
stamped LDPE.
lt should be molded
right into the plastic.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, LDPE.
Right on, got it.
l don't know, man.
This feels kind of flimsy.
Any decent acid's
gonna eat right through this.
Not hydrofluoric.
Why not?
Look, you skipped,
clowned around
or otherwise jerked off through
every lecture l ever gave.
As far as l'm concerned,
your chemistry education is over.
Oh, okay, be a dick about it.
Jesus.
So, hey, have you, um...?
Have you done the--?
The thing?
Yeah, l'm--
l'm working up to it.
[WHlSPERlNG]
You know what?
l bet he doesn't even wake up.
You know, not even
if you took him
to the hospital right now.
Now, if it was me,
l would just try and think of it
like l was--
l was doing him a favor.
[BEEPS]
MAN [OVER PA]:
l need a check approval
on checkstand eight.
Approval on checkstand eight,
please. Thank you.
[SlGHS]
Yeah.
[GRUNTS]
[♪♪♪]
KRAZY-8:
Who's there?
What, you fucking break in?
Show me who's there.
Yeah. l see you.
What you gonna do?
Hey.
Hey--!
[COUGHlNG]
Hey!
l need water.
[COUGHlNG]
Hey, hello.
Bring me some water,
would you?
[COUGHlNG]
Please.
You don't like the crust?
Where's my cousin Emilio?
He dead?
[DOOR SLAMS]
[KRAZY-8 COUGHlNG]
Oh, l'm a coward.
[♪♪♪]
[SlGHS]
[COUGHlNG]
[DOOR OPENS]
JESSE:
Hey, Mr. White.
Hey, Mr. White?
Oh, fuck.
[CHUCKLlNG]
Are you smoking weed?
Oh, my God.
Wait a minute, is that--?
ls that my weed?
What the hell, man?
Make yourself at home,
why don't you?
So, what'd you end up buying?
Nothing.
No store in town sells a plastic
bin big enough for a body.
l don't suppose
you could buy two bins?
And, uh, just:
Legs in one,
torso in the other?
Oh, God.
l don't suppose
you could kiss my ass?
[SlGHS]
So, uh,
how'd it--? How'd it go?
[KRAZY-8 COUGHlNG]
You didn't do it?
Not-- Not yet.
Oh, God.
Oh, damn. l gotta go.
Hey, hey.
What? No, no, no.
Come back here.
Sorry. l'll do it tomorrow,
l promise.
Tomorrow?
l've got a doctor's appointment.
l gotta go.
Look, stay away from him.
He's awake.
[DOOR OPENS]
Hey, man, we flipped a coin.
[DOOR CLOSES]
[KRAZY-8 COUGHlNG]
We flipped a coin!
We're-- We're good?
We're very good.
We're excellent, l'd say.
Oh.
Oh, would you look
at that face?
[ALL CHUCKLE]
Smile, peanut.
So who's up for knowing?
Oh...
Uh. ..
[BOTH LAUGH]
lt's-- lt's...
Uh. ..
Yeah.
Girl.
Girl?
You sure?
OB-GYN: Pretty sure.
[BOTH LAUGH]
Wow.
Oh, God. Can l tell you,
that's exactly what l was hoping.
Yeah?
Yeah.
You remember you said that
when she's 1 6 and starts dating.
[SKYLER LAUGHS]
OB-GYN:
Looking fabulous.
Let me see if they're done
with the blood sugar,
then we'll get you out of here.
l'll be right back.
Who's Jesse Pinkman?
Jesse...?
Jesse Pinkman.
He-- He called
just this morning.
Walt, please don't deny it.
Oh, uh, yeah, yeah, yeah.
lt-- lt says on his MyShout page
he attended Wynne.
What, was he one
of your students?
Yeah.
He was nobody.
Who--? Who is he to you?
Why--? Why is he calling?
What is this big secret
you seem to be discussing
with some druggie burnout?
You don't come home last night
until 2 in the morning.
You don't tell me
where you've been.
You spent the entire night
in the bathroom, Walt.
Tell me what's going on
with you.
Don't you think
you owe me that?
Who is this Jesse Pinkman
to you?
He sells me pot.
He sells you pot?
Marijuana, yeah.
Not a lot.
l mean, l don't know.
[SlGHS]
l kind of like it.
Are you out of your mind?
What--? What are you, like,
1 6 years old?
Your brother-in-law
is a DEA agent.
What--?
What is wrong with you?
Look, Skyler,
[SlGHS]
l just haven't
quite been myself lately.
Yeah. No shit.
Thanks for noticing.
l haven't been myself lately,
but l love you.
Nothing about that
has changed.
Nothing ever will.
So right now, what l need
is for you to climb down
out of my ass.
Can you do that?
Will you do that for me, honey?
Will you please, just once,
get off my ass?
You know.
l'd appreciate it.
l really would.
Stop.
Stop in-- ln 1 5 minutes.
[COUGHS]
[♪♪♪]
[SNORTS]
SHEMP [OVER TV]:
Your face is too sharp.
MOE [OVER TV]:
Powder. Powder!
SHEMP:
Take a powder, go on.
[KRAZY-8 COUGHlNG]
MOE:
Nice. Beautiful talcum powder.
Lucky you, number eight.
[SNEEZES]
Just meat, it's all just--
Just a bunch of meat.
[FLlES BUZZlNG]
Oh, Jesus.
[GROANlNG]
You're cool,
you're cool.
You're all good, you're all--
You're all good. You know it.
lt's fine.
lt's just a bunch of meat.
Come on. You're good.
[PANTlNG]
Excuse me.
Excuse me. You. Yes, you.
May l talk to you?
Oh, whoa, whoa, whoa,
hey, hey, hey.
This is private property.
Just a minute.
l-- l wanna talk to you.
No, no, not interested. Come on.
SKYLER: Hey, don't touch me.
Do not touch me.
All right, all right, look,
not touching, okay?
Not touching here.
Look, lady,
whatever you're selling,
l ain't buying, yo.
Well, my name
is Skyler White, yo.
My husband
is Walter White, yo.
Uh-huh.
He told me everything.
Seriously?
That's right.
And just so you know,
my brother-in-law
is a DEA agent
and l will not hesitate
to call him.
Not if l have to.
Understood?
This is your one
and only warning.
Do not sell marijuana
to my husband.
Okay.
l mean it.
Don't call our house again.
You stay away from him, or
you will be one sorry individual.
You get me?
l-- l , uh, think so, yeah.
Um, no more marijuana.
Mm-hm.
l can-- l can dig it.
You can dig it. Wonderful.
Not that it's any
of my business,
but you might wanna consider
a different line of work.
Okay.
[SlGHS]
[GRUNTlNG AND PANTlNG]
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
Let's go to your house,
you know.
Makes perfect sense.
Let's, uh...
[GASPlNG]
let's completely screw up
your house
so you never wanna spend
another night in it.
Sure. You know, why not?
[GRUNTlNG]
Yeah, and how's about l send
over my psycho-bitch wife
to, uh, you know, break your
balls and threaten you?
God, that would be hilarious,
you know.
And then, you know,
the killer in the basement,
the one who's completely
my responsibility,
hell, let's just
let him live down there.
Just, l don't know, make sure
to feed him, like,
three times a day.
Sure, why not?
lt's been really amazing.
Thank you so much
for the opportunity.
l always dreamt about,
l don't know, melting bodies.
[JESSE WHlMPERS
THEN COUGHS]
[GROANlNG]
[DOOR OPENS]
[DOOR CLOSES]
You got a brother
in the goddamn DEA?
What?
You said you were just doing
some ride-along.
Yes or no, do you have a brother
in the DEA?
He's a brother-in-law.
Oh, well, there's a load
off my mind.
Where did you hear that?
Your freaking wife told me
when she was here
all up in my shit.
Yeah, that's right.
She almost caught me
moving Emilio.
Good job on wearing
the pants in the family.
And why'd you go and tell her
l was selling you weed?
Because somehow
it seemed preferable
to admitting that l cook
crystal meth and killed a man.
[SNlFFlNG]
ls that what l think it is?
Yeah. Yeah, it is.
l smoked a bowl.
So what?
My house, my rules.
Hey, no, no.
Hey, don't give me that, okay?
l held up my end.
l already took care
of Emilio.
You're still diddling around
trying to get your nut up.
Yeah, well, boo-hoo.
l have the truly awful job here.
Oh, you wanna-- You wanna talk
awful? You wanna go there?
Try dragging 200 pounds of stink
up a flight of stairs.
l barely got him in the bathtub.
Bathtub, what...?
What do you mean, bathtub?
You know,
and that's another thing.
Why you got me
running around town
trying to find
some stupid piece of plastic
when l have a perfectly good tub
l can use?
Oh, God.
Hey. Hey.
[DRlPPlNG]
[HlSSlNG]
[SlGHS]
l'm sorry, what were you
asking me? Oh, yes.
That stupid plastic container
l asked you to buy.
You see, hydrofluoric acid
won't eat through plastic.
lt will, however, dissolve
metal, rock, glass, ceramic.
So there's that.
[GLEN PHlLLlPS' "THE HOLE"
PLAYS]
BOY:
Here l go.